Where are we
我们在哪里
thai police
泰国警察
Now I suspect you've reached your limit
现在我怀疑你已经到了极限
within national borders
在国界内
What? Is there espionage?
什么？有间谍活动吗？
did you take it
你拿了吗
Sample bottles to the border
样品瓶到边境
if
如果
Isn’t this the mission of the game?
这不就是游戏的使命吗？
answer my question
回答我的问题
if i say
如果我说
Will it break?
会坏吗？
game over
游戏失败
answer my question
回答我的问题
Bounds entered with the sample
与样本一起输入的边界
What is your goal?
你的目标是什么？
I do not know anything
我什么都不知道
You are wrong
您错了
Do you think you can be fooled?
你以为你能骗得了你吗？
honestly
诚实地
i am confident of success
我对成功充满信心
This round has been decided
本轮已决
I can tell you what you said
我可以告诉你你说的话
Is what you said true or false?
你说的是真是假
What's this
这是什么
What's your job?
你做什么工作？
next question
下一个问题
Please answer truthfully
请如实回答
It's a lying device
这是一个说谎的装置
take it
拿着它
I am not very good
我不是很好
If you lie, you will feel uncomfortable
如果你撒谎，你会感到不舒服
Can I ask you a question?
我可以问你一个问题吗？
The girl who came with me before
之前跟我一起来的那个女孩
that girl
那个女孩
you have no right to ask
你没有权利询问
Is the answer correct or not?
答案正确与否
concept?
概念？
Yes.
是的。
Is your name Huang Zicheng?
你叫黄子成吗？
Yes
是的
are you a man?
你是个男人吗？
It is clear
很明显
Yes
是的
Are you the President of the United States?
你是美国总统吗？
Actual electricity consumption
实际用电
every time i make a mistake
每次我犯错的时候
Electricity bill doubled
电费翻倍
Kind tips
温馨提示
Are you the President of the United States?
你是美国总统吗？
No
不
Data is extracted
数据被提取
you can start
你可以开始了
Let's get started
让我们正式开始吧
Is Yaoyao your partner?
瑶瑶是你的搭档吗？
Yes
是的
really
确实
Have you told anyone?
你告诉过任何人吗？
Online homework?
网上作业？
No
不
forged
锻造的
No, not there
不，那里没有
from
从
I can't answer
我无法回答
to answer your question
来回答你这个问题
the third time
第三次
current
电流
8 times the starting condition
起始条件的8倍
I have I have
我有 我有
I have a friend named Jiang Xiaohua
我有一个朋友叫姜小花
She also knows
她也知道
Did you tell her?
你告诉她了吗？
Mission content?
任务内容？
No
不
Really?
真的吗？
Have you received any special training?
你接受过特殊训练吗？
Yes.
是的。
really
确实
Do you know what a sample is?
你知道什么是样本吗？
No
不
really
确实
Are you a CIA agent?
你是中央情报局特工吗？
Yes
是的
really
确实
Are you workers of your planet?
你们是你们星球的工人吗？
Yes
是的
really
确实
Are you an agent of the Chinese Security Bureau?
你是中国安全局的特工吗？
Yes
是的
really
确实
Is it between you and Yaoyao?
是你和瑶瑶之间吗
Between you and Yaoyaoyao
你和瑶瑶瑶之间
No
不
really
确实
Do you love her?
你爱她吗？
No
不
forged
锻造的
i kinda like her
我有点喜欢她
Did you hide the sample?
你把样本藏起来了吗？
In your eyes?
在你眼里？
Yes
是的
really
确实
Are you still not satisfied?
你还不满意吗？
I have no choice
我别无选择
are you serious?
你是认真的？
very difficult
非常艰难
remember
记住
as long as i tell the truth
只要我说真话
there will be no pain
不会有疼痛
admit defeat
承认失败
Where are the samples hidden?
样本藏在哪里？
Sample is hidden
样本被隐藏
In the kitchen trash can
在厨房的垃圾桶里
any trash can
任何垃圾桶
I don't remember either
我也不记得了
in the kitchen anyway
无论如何在厨房里
Are samples hidden?
样本被隐藏了吗？
kitchen in cafe
咖啡厅里的厨房
Yes
是的
really
确实
I can take you to find it
我可以带你去找
but in you
但在你身上
Let Yaoyao go first
先放了瑶瑶
you really love your partner
你真的很爱你的伴侣
I hid that thing
我把那东西藏起来了
You can't hurt her
你不能连累她
OK
好的
Are you OK?
你好吗？
I am fine
我很好
I told you
我告诉过你
Where do you hide your stuff?
你把东西藏在哪里？
do you remember?
你是否记得？
I remember
我记得
Guangtu is coming
光土来了
Are you a dummy?
你是傻子吗？
Do not you know me?
你不认识我吗？
Who are you
你是谁
sorry
对不起
I was wrong
我错了
Sorry, I was wrong
对不起，我错了
Hurry up
快快快
Go quickly
快去
back door
后门
God I'm so tired
天啊我好累
look
看
Great, you succeeded again
太好了，你又成功了
let's go
我们走吧
Is this it?
这是吗？
perhaps
或许
let's go
我们走吧
Do you love her?
你爱她吗？
No
不
forged
锻造的
i kind of like him
我有点喜欢他
Did they ask you?
他们有问你吗？
this problem
这个问题
How did you answer?
你怎么回答的？
I
我
Congratulations to both of you
恭喜你们俩
You have completed this e-task
您已完成此电子任务
I passed
我通过了
why is it you again?
怎么又是你？
Now
现在
Can you give me samples?
你能给我样品吗？
this existence
这个存在
But no cryopreservation
但没有低温保存
I don't know if it can be used
不知道能不能用
The mission of these tools
这些工具的使命
among these tools
在这些工具中
I've dealt with you many times
我已经和你打交道很多次了
I do not know who you are
我不知道你是谁
I am a private employee
我是一名私人雇员
perform special mission
执行特殊使命
Tony
托尼
i can be a thai policeman
我可以成为泰国警察
CIA
中央情报局
it is a planet
它是一颗行星
maybe china
可能是中国
this means
这意味着
These people are all actors
这些人都是演员
unnecessary
不必要
this may be true
这可能是真的
No
不
this game is cool
这个游戏很酷
Every interview is personal
每次采访都是私人的
you need to lie
你需要撒谎
we use
我们用
CIA standards
中央情报局标准
trial
审讯
this is an important part
这是一个重要的部分
important part
重要部分
This is a double test
这是双重考验
double test
双重测试
special mission
特殊使命
the most important thing
最重要的事情
it's bringing back the truth
它正在带回真相
this is amazing
这真太了不起了
All are online challenges
都是线上挑战
You must try it
你一定要尝试一下
Really good
真的很棒
if there is no partner
如果没有伙伴
I won't be able to get over this
我将无法克服这一点
The following two answers
下面两个答案
difficulty will increase
难度会增加
this means
这意味着
you are closer
你更近了
Another step
又一步
looking forward to it
期待它
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
Nice scene
场景不错
you have put in a lot of effort
你已经付出了很多努力
This game was really designed
这游戏真的是设计出来的
deadly specimen lies
致命的标本躺着
and this
和这个
thai police
泰国警察
many moments
很多时刻
I thought this was a real event
我以为这是一个真实的事件
it's like
这就像
Zhou Min's world
周敏的世界
Do you think this is true?
你认为这是真的吗？
In fact, everything has been arranged
其实一切都已经安排好了
you are right
你是对的
after that
在那之后
It's getting harder and harder
越来越难了
Will you continue?
你会继续吗？
nature
自然
I'm addicted to playing
我玩上瘾了
Me too
我也是
I started to look forward to
我开始期待
at the next stage
在下一阶段
Where are we going now?
我们现在去哪里？
Now
现在
Let's hide the stress
我们去隐藏压力吧
I will accompany you until the end
我会陪你到最后
let's go
我们走吧
they succeeded
他们成功了
OK
好的
Be prepared to tidy up
准备好收拾一下
truly special mission
真正的特殊使命
OK
好的
Pull out the violin statue
拉出小提琴雕像
welcome
欢迎
you
你
sit
坐
you have done your job
你已经完成你的工作了
Did you bring any money?
你带钱来了吗？
Yes
是的
twenty thousand
二十千
here
这里
And one more thing
还有一件事
no thanks
不，谢谢
Hi pretty girl
你好美女
drink
喝
I don't drink
我不喝
don't worry
别着急
drink
喝
leave me
离开我
Are you drunk?
你醉了吗？
a lot of money
很多钱
Beautiful where are you going?
美丽的你要去哪里？
give me the bag
把包给我
leave me
离开我
Why did you steal my bag?
你为什么偷我的包？
I'm going out
我出去了
Sir, please leave quickly.
先生快点走吧
Who are you
你是谁
Brother Wei
韦弟兄
I want to ask you something
我想问你点事儿
Who are you
你是谁
that girl
那个女孩
Why are you looking for me?
你为什么找我？
which girl
哪个女孩
the girl who just left
刚刚离开的女孩
She's here to apply for a passport
她是来办护照的
Do you know about fake certificates?
你知道假证书吗？
he's done it before
他以前做过
Fake National Security Investigation Certificate
假国家安全调查证明
he was arrested
他被捕了
Make fake passports
制作假护照
he might run away
他可能会逃跑
unable to sit down
无法坐下
He can't bear the psychological pressure
他无法承受心理压力
That's why it's risky
这就是风险的原因
Do you think anything is mine?
你认为有什么东西是我的吗？
You guess there's something wrong with her
你猜她有问题
Maybe I've known it for a long time
也许我已经知道很久了
why are you there
你为什么在那儿
After quarreling with you
和你吵架后
I'll go out and calm down
我出去冷静一下
I saw you coming out
我看见你出来了
what happened?
发生了什么？
How did you get to this place?
你是怎么到这个地方的？
I went to buy a passport
我去买护照了
I went and bought a fake passport
我去买了假护照
you are crazy
你疯了
yes i'm crazy
是的，我疯了
if i don't leave
如果我不离开
i will lose my mind
我会失去理智
Can you calm down a little?
你能冷静一点吗？
I can't calm down
我无法平静
what have you done?
你做了什么？
I
我
You stole the lab sample
你偷了实验室样本
say it again
再说一次
I said I stole it
我说我偷了
laboratory samples
实验室样品
What's your job?
你做什么工作？
Do not ask
不要问
I'm a mess now
我现在一团糟
you have committed a crime
你已经犯罪了
they can catch me anytime
他们随时可以抓住我
so i'm leaving
所以我要离开了
I'll leave now
我现在就离开
If I didn't have a passport I would run away
如果我没有护照我就会逃跑
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
I have to get out of here
我必须离开这里
you can't leave
你不能离开
Would you think so if you went out?
如果你出去的话你会这样想吗？
go out
出去
what happened
发生了什么
Tian Yang
田阳
Listen, Yu Xiaoyu
听着，于晓宇
confess something to me
向我坦白一件事
Sample theft
样品失窃
I have no choice
我别无选择
I now how to do?
我现在该怎么办？
They withheld my passport
他们扣留了我的护照
They know I stole it
他们知道我偷了
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
something for me
给我的东西
please give me something
请给我一些东西
Please help me
请帮我
I beg you
我求求你
Why did you do this?
你为什么这么做？
they are threatening me
他们在威胁我
from
从
gentlemen
先生
That is, professor
也就是教授
he is professor
他是教授
professor
教授
I have published
我已经发布
in foreign newspapers
在国外的报纸上
Use experimental data
使用实验数据
Experimental data
实验数据
He threatened me with this
他用这个威胁我
He asked me to help him
他请我帮助他
For more data, see the Institute
更多数据请见研究所
so i took
所以我采取了
I thought I would take it with me
我以为我会带着它
I have no expectations
我没有期待
he is threatening me
他在威胁我
He asked me to steal samples
他让我偷样品
Yu Xiaoyu
于晓宇
You better steal secrets to escape
你最好窃取秘密才能逃脱
worth
值得
I
我
I want to go out
我想出去
I have a
我有一个
Admission Notice from British Columbia, Australia
澳大利亚BC省录取通知书
I have to go
我得走了
Do you think you can leave?
你觉得你可以离开吗？
Why can't I leave?
为什么我不能离开？
I have a passport
我有护照
no benefit
没有好处
look by youself
你自己看
not even there
甚至不在那里
there is nothing
没有什么
How could it be true?
怎么可能是真的呢？
You can't even get through customs
你连海关都过不了
impossible
不可能的
I'm done
我受够了
There is only one way now
现在只有一个办法
what is it?
它是什么？
I admit
我承认
I admit?
我承认？
Do you want me to turn myself in?
你想让我自首吗？
I do not want
我不想要
I can't go to jail
我不能去监狱
i'm in jail
我在监狱里
If you can recover the sample
如果你能恢复样本
If no loss is caused
如果没有造成任何损失
He will not be sentenced to death
他不会被判处死刑
implement?
执行？
I will be sentenced to death
我将被判处死刑
i have to give up
我必须放弃
something for me
给我的东西
do you hate me?
你恨我吗？
i know you hate me
我知道你恨我
I would rather die
我宁可死
don't let me go
别让我走
Yu Xiaoyu
于晓宇
you made it yourself
你自己做的
Surrender is your only option
投降是你唯一的选择
No
不
I don't want to give up on myself
我不想放弃自己
Why should I give up?
我为什么要放弃？
I give up I want to go to jail
我放弃我想进监狱
I don't want to go to jail
我不想坐牢
How many years should I go to jail?
我应该入狱多少年？
i have grown up
我已经长大了
my life will end
我的生命将结束
I don't want to go to jail
我不想进监狱
Don't they know it yet?
他们还不知道吗？
something for me
给我的东西
They haven't discovered this yet
他们还没有发现这一点
Do not say
不要说
Please help me
请帮我
I don't want to go to jail
我不想进监狱
please
请
help me
帮我
I really don't want to go to jail
我真的不想进监狱
I really
我真的
something for me
给我的东西
Didn't you say you love me?
你不是说你爱我吗？
Didn't you say that?
你没说吗？
you will love me forever
你会永远爱我
help me
帮我
I really don't want to go to jail
我真的不想进监狱
please
请
if you listen to me
如果你听我说
How did you get to this point today?
你今天怎么走到这一步了？
everything i do
我所做的一切
You do everything yourself
一切都是你自己做的
think about it
想想看
In order to gain recognition, there is another way to survive
为了得到认可，还有一种活法
Escape is a road to death
逃亡是一条通往死亡的道路
Blackfish will throw you into the sea
黑鱼会把你扔进海里
Or sell you abroad
或者把你卖到国外
you got me involved
你让我参与其中
If I run away I'm guilty
如果我逃跑了 我就有罪
I'll help you write the topic
我帮你写题目写
Help you clarify relationships and join the group
帮助你理清关系，进群
everything i do
我所做的一切
He will make me your partner
他会让我成为你的伙伴
Yu Xiaoyu
于晓宇
you always think about yourself
你总是为自己着想
Don't consider other people's feelings at all
根本不考虑别人的感受
Come on, Yu Xiaoyu
加油，于小雨
let me ask you
让我问问你
Have you ever thought about your mother?
你有想过你的母亲吗？
you didn't miss me
你没有想念我
do not speak
不要说话
She hopes to stay in Tianhai
她希望留在天海
Go to the Institute
前往研究所
One day I will bring her here
有一天我会带她来这里
But what are you thinking?
但你在想什么？
Live streaming is very popular
直播很受欢迎
Travel abroad and be surrounded by gold
出国旅游，被黄金包围
He met a rich and handsome man
他遇到了一个又富又帅的男人
And your bag
还有你的包包
because of your arrogance
因为你的傲慢
if you don't want to go to jail
如果你不想进监狱
There are only two ways
只有两个办法
Either surrender
要么投降
or you die
或者你死了
Shri leaves
施莉离开了
He carefully observed Xiao Yue's situation
他仔细观察着萧月的情况
let's leave now
我们现在就走
Are you worried about Yu Xiaoyu?
你担心于小雨吗？
What's in it for me?
对我来说有什么用？
she is the only one
她是唯一一个
Now is the last straw to save her
现在是拯救她的最后一根稻草
I also fell
我也跌倒了
Yu Xiaoyu was seriously injured
于晓宇伤势严重
accept espionage organization
接受间谍组织
and lawyer
和律师
This leads us to
这导致我们
serious losses
损失严重
and gain political rights
并获得政治权利
property
tịch thu 财产
He was sentenced to 10 years in prison
他被判处10年徒刑
Life imprisonment or death penalty
无期徒刑或死刑
I don't want to go to jail
我不想进监狱
I don't want to face this world
我不想面对这个世界
Don't tell my mother the truth
不要告诉我妈妈真相
Message from Yu Xiaoyu
余小雨发来的消息
something went wrong
出了点问题
I don't want to go to jail
我不想进监狱
I don't want to face this world
我不想面对这个世界
Don't tell my mother the truth
不要告诉我妈妈真相
you will die
你会死
call the ambulance
叫救护车
OK
好的
Yu Xiaoyu
于晓宇
Xiao Chen turns off the gas light
小陈关掉煤气灯
OK
好的
open the door
打开门
Yu Xiaoyu
于晓宇
I woke up
我醒了
Yu Xiaoyu woke up
于小雨醒来了
When will the ambulance arrive?
救护车什么时候到达？
Instantly
立即地
Take it out first
先拿出来
Take her out quickly
快点带她出去
Hurry up
快快快
Take it easy
慢慢来
something for me
给我的东西
welcome
欢迎
We are Kimhae National Security Bureau
我们是金海国安局
we want to talk to you
我们想和你谈谈
Welcome to enter
欢迎您进入
What’s wrong with you
你怎么了
there is nothing
没有什么
I feel fever
我感觉发烧
Can you stand trial?
你能接受审讯吗？
perhaps
或许
sit
坐
Yu Xiaoyu is in trouble
于小雨遇到麻烦了
did you know?
你可知道？
What's up with her?
她怎么了？
suicide
自杀
What did you say?
你说什么？
she committed suicide
她自杀了
Is she dead?
她死了吗？
Do you know why she committed suicide?
你知道她为什么自杀吗？
something for me
给我的东西
Yu Xiaoyu committed suicide
于晓宇自杀
Didn't you notice?
你没注意到吗？
I never thought she would commit suicide
没想到她会自杀
Did I send it to you?
我发给你了吗
I sent you a message
我给你发了一条消息
I don't know, I lost my phone
我不知道，我手机丢了
Where did you lose?
你输在哪里了？
I fell into the sea
我掉进海里
Did you go to her house today?
今天你去她家了吗？
Yes
是的
Didn't you notice?
你没注意到吗？
She is emotionally unstable
她的情绪不稳定
I shouldn't force her
我不应该强迫她
I shouldn't argue with her
我不应该和她争吵
I'm the one who hurt her
我才是伤害她的人
What did you force her to do?
你强迫她做什么？
I advised her to surrender
我劝她投降
Laboratory samples stolen
实验室样本被盗
how do you know
你怎么知道
She told me personally
她亲口告诉我的
Why did you commit suicide?
你为什么自杀？
she committed suicide
她自杀了
I
我
I have no idea
我不知道
what do you know?
你知道什么？
she was threatened
她被威胁了
Who are you
你是谁
gentlemen
先生
any professor
任何教授
I do not know him
我不认识他
I only know
我只知道
She was conducting a study in Australia
她当时正在澳大利亚进行一项研究
When I was studying in Australia
我在澳洲读书的时候
that person
那个人
in the process of disseminating information
在传播信息的过程中
one move
一招
Data and samples
数据和样本
then threaten her
然后威胁她
Let her continue stealing
让她继续偷
Data and samples
数据和样本
You have
你有
contact number
联系电话
Xiao Yueyou
小悦有
It was they who summoned them.
是他们召唤了他们
you are her lover
你是她的爱人
How could you not know?
你怎么会不知道呢？
about this person
关于这个人
I called a professor
我打电话给一位教授
with professor
和教授一起
Why
为什么
Maybe I am against her going abroad
也许我反对她出国
I have a good job here
我在这里有一份好工作
steady development
稳定发展
Why did you leave China?
你为什么离开中国？
I do not understand
我不明白
but she didn't listen
但她不听
if you go
如果你走
you will break up
你会分手
perhaps
或许
Didn't you think of any other way?
你就没有想到别的办法吗？
accept
收下
Yes
是的
I'm the one who hurt her
我才是伤害她的人
Study abroad
海外留学
You need to post
您需要发帖
In Power Abroad magazine
在《Power Abroad》杂志上
If you promise to help her first
如果你答应先帮助她
then
当时
you must not steal
你不可以偷窃
Search data
搜索数据
data
数据
he won't be there
他不会在那里
more and more
越来越多
Do you hate her?
你讨厌她吗？
I hate myself
我恨我自己
It seems you really love her
看来你真的很爱她
Love her
爱她
but it changed
但它改变了
she is famous on the internet
她在网络上出名
everything has changed
一切都变了
Play on her ego
利用她的自负
Yes or no
是不是
Who wouldn't be proud now?
现在谁不感到自豪呢？
can you play?
你能玩吗？
No
不
So be it
就这样吧
Can't leave the city for the time being
暂时不能离开城市
if anything
如果有什么的话
We'll always find you
我们随时找到您
Can you tell me?
你能告诉我吗？
Xiao, is Xiao Yu dead?
萧，萧宇死了吗？
he is still in coma
他仍处于昏迷状态
Finally I'm back
终于我回来了
let me clarify it for you
让我为你澄清
OK
好的
Do you feel cold?
你觉得冷吗？
a little
一点
Wipe it too
也擦一下
welcome
欢迎
Huang Ziqing this afternoon
黄子晴今天下午
this afternoon
今天下午
You came back alone
你一个人回来了
that player
那个玩家
Not with him anymore
不再和他在一起了
He came back by himself this morning
今天早上他自己回来了
How will you treat them?
你将如何对待他们？
we want you to know the truth
我们想让你知道真相
You are from the district office
你是区公所的
Don't you know this is in Thailand?
你不知道这是在泰国吗？
What is he doing
他在做什么
we know
我们知道
but not completely
但并不完全
Already withdrawn?
已经撤回了吗？
As far as I know, not yet
据我所知，还没有
This is good
这很好
do not you?
你不是吗？
Do you trust him?
你信任他吗？
Not Ye Wu's opponent
不是夜雾的对手
So we need to monitor more
所以我们要多加监控
from the night fog
从夜雾中
Will look for it again
会再找找
already
已经是
This is our breakthrough
这是我们的突破
we need to monitor
我们需要监控
Huang Zhicheng’s abacus
黄志成的算盘
I have
我有
in game
在游戏里
this matter
这件事
It's not difficult for you
对你来说不难
let him continue playing
让他继续玩
When one day he understands
当有一天他明白
The horse stopped on the edge of the cliff
马停在悬崖边
Or you trust him
或者你信任他
you have enough brains
你有足够的脑子
to resist spies
为了抵抗间谍
I've known you for a long time
我认识你很久了
This is the first time I discovered it
这是我第一次发现它
You are very reluctant to work
你非常不愿意工作
Psychological science doesn’t ask you to analyze
心理科学不要求你去分析
your partner
你的搭档
you know
你知道
this is the best way
这是最好的方法
you must be uncomfortable
你一定不舒服
I'll get you a cup of coffee
我给你倒杯咖啡
ok sit there
好吧坐那儿
You're welcome
不客气
I can do it myself, come back
我自己可以，回来吧
Hi brother
你好兄弟
Where did you play?
你在哪里玩的？
Your phone is turned off
你的手机已关机
I went to Thailand
我去了泰国
I just got off the plane
我刚下飞机
Are you OK
你好吗
don't mention it
别提它
Let's go home and have dinner
我们回家吃晚饭吧
Can I not go?
我可以不去吗？
No
不
if you don't come
如果你不来
Lao Huang will go find you
老黄就去找你
I know I know
我知道，我知道
Laohuang serial port connection
老黄串口连接
I called him
我打过电话给他
I tell you
我告诉你
Be nice when you come back
回来后要乖一点
I disappeared during this time
我在这段时间消失了
he has a good opinion
他有一个很好的意见
OK
好的
see you tonight
今晚见
You must speak for me
你必须帮我说话
i will provide
我会提供
Dad, I'm sorry
爸爸，对不起
I shouldn't be missing
我不应该失踪
you should have
你应该有
Send me abroad
送我出国
What to do in Thailand
去泰国可以做什么
I am playing game
我玩游戏
another game
另一场比赛
there is a game
有一场比赛
Don't you want to play?
你不想玩吗？
This time is different
这次不同
this is a new way
这是一种新方式
online
在线的
Offline again
再次掉线
it's just a game
这只是一个游戏
if i go with you
如果我和你一起去
Not the same thing
不是同一个东西
More exciting than before
比之前更刺激
The most important thing is the bonus
最重要的是奖金
It happened several times before
之前有过几次
How much higher?
高多少？
We have to wait until he succeeds
我们必须等到他成功
so that we can get it
这样我们就可以得到它
slowly
慢慢地
past
过去
has been arrested
已被逮捕
marketing fraud organization
营销诈骗组织
This is in Thailand
这是在泰国
how do you look
你看起来怎么样
very similar
非常相似
What is my photo?
我的照片是什么？
in your heart
在你心里
If you say I joined a cult
如果你说我加入了邪教
Do you believe me?
你相信我吗？
There is no such possibility
没有这个可能
You do not understand
你不明白
And you want to ask
而你想问
I do not want to talk to you
我不想和你说话
Anyway, please remember
无论如何，请记住
play games
玩游戏
money can be made
钱是可以赚到的
no risk
没有风险
enough
就够了
You are becoming more and more like a cult
你们越来越像邪教了
Brown
棕色的
Let's play online
我们在线玩吧
I am now
我现在是
he
他
Don't go to jail.
别进监狱。
my uncle.
我的叔叔。
he knows what to do
他知道该怎么做
At most, you can cheat some money
顶多骗点钱
fool with some colors
愚弄一些颜色
if you break the law
如果您违法
It turns out not
原来不是
this is correct
这是对的
What? this is correct
什么？这是对的
You believe everything my brother says
我哥哥说的一切你都相信
No
不
Can't you be by my side?
你就不能在我身边吗？
and set fire to
并放火
Why are you so evil?
你为什么这么邪恶？
Okay, okay, let's not talk.
好吧好吧我们不说话
let's drink
我们喝吧
Dad didn't listen to him
爸爸不听他的话
Don't you understand what good or bad words are?
难道你不明白什么是好话或坏话吗？
Lao Huang has little drinking ability
老黄喝酒能力小
always like to show off
总是喜欢炫耀
Looks like you can drink it
看来可以喝
do not give up
不要放弃
let's go
我们走吧